http://www.lutyenstrust.org.uk/terms-and-conditions/

loading...
TERMS OF WEBSITE USE
This page (together with the documents referred to on it) tells you the terms of use on which you may make use of our websites at www.lutyenstrust.org.uk, www.lutyenstrustexhibitions.org.uk and www.lutyenstrustexhibitions1.org.uk (together, our site), whether as a guest or a registered user. Please read these terms of use carefully before you start to use the site. By using our site, you indicate that you accept these terms of use and that you agree to abide by them. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please refrain from using our site.
INFORMATION ABOUT US
www.lutyenstrust.org.uk is a website operated by The Lutyens Trust “We”). We are a registered charity in England and Wales, with number 326776. Our main address is Goddards, Abinger Common, Dorking, Surrey RH5 6JH.
ACCESSING OUR SITE
Access to our site is permitted on a temporary basis, and we reserve the right to withdraw or amend the service we provide on our site without notice (see below). We will not be liable if for any reason our site is unavailable at any time or for any period.
From time to time, we may restrict access to some parts of our site, or our entire site, to users who have registered with us.
If you choose, or you are provided with, a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential, and you must not disclose it to any third party. We have the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or allocated by us, at any time, if in our opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these terms of use.
When using our site, you must comply with the provisions of our Acceptable Use Policy.
You are responsible for making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to our site. You are also responsible for ensuring that all persons who access our site through your internet connection are aware of these terms, and that they comply with them.
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS
We are the owner or licensee of all intellectual property rights in our site or have obtained all necessary permissions and consents relating to the material published on it. Those works are protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world. All such rights are reserved.
You may print off one copy, and may download extracts, of any page(s) from our site for your personal reference and you may draw the attention of others within your organisation to material posted on our site.
You must not modify the paper or digital copies of any materials you have printed off or downloaded in any way, and you must not use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics separately from any accompanying text.
Our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of material on our site must always be acknowledged.
You must not use any part of the materials on our site for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or our licensors.
If you print off, copy or download any part of our site in breach of these terms of use, your right to use our site will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made.
RELIANCE ON INFORMATION POSTED
Commentary and other materials posted on our site are not intended to amount to advice on which reliance should be placed. We therefore disclaim all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by any visitor to our site, or by anyone who may be informed of any of its contents.
SITE CHANGES
We aim to update our site regularly, and may change the content at any time. If the need arises, we may suspend access to our site, or close it indefinitely. Any of the material on our site may be out of date at any given time, and we are under no obligation to update such material.
OUR LIABILITY
The material displayed on our site is provided without any guarantees, conditions or warranties as to its accuracy. To the extent permitted by law, we and third parties connected to us hereby expressly exclude:
•All conditions, warranties and other terms which might otherwise be implied by statute, common law or the law of equity.
•Any liability for any direct, indirect or consequential loss or damage incurred by any user in connection with our site or in connection with the use, inability to use, or results of the use of our site, any websites linked to it and any materials posted on it, including:
•loss of income or revenue;
•loss of business;
•loss of profits or contracts;
•loss of anticipated savings;
•loss of data;
•loss of goodwill; and
•wasted management or office time,
whether caused by tort (including negligence), breach of contract or otherwise, even if foreseeable.
This does not affect our liability for death or personal injury arising from our negligence, nor our liability for fraudulent misrepresentation or misrepresentation as to a fundamental matter, nor any other liability which cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law.
INFORMATION ABOUT YOU AND YOUR VISITS TO OUR SITE
We process information about you in accordance with our Privacy Policy. By using our site, you consent to such processing and you warrant that all data provided by you is accurate.
UPLOADING MATERIAL TO OUR SITE
Whenever you make use of a feature that allows you to upload material to our site, or to make contact with other users of our site, you must comply with the content standards set out in our Acceptable Use Policy. You warrant that any such contribution does comply with those standards, and you indemnify us for any breach of that warranty.
Any material you upload to our site will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary, and we have the right to use, copy, distribute and disclose to third parties any such material for any purpose. We also have the right to disclose your identity to any third party who is claiming that any material posted or uploaded by you to our site constitutes a violation of their intellectual property rights, or of their right to privacy.
We will not be responsible, or liable to any third party, for the content or accuracy of any materials posted by you or any other user of our site.
We have the right to remove any material or posting you make on our site if, in our opinion, such material does not comply with the content standards set out in our Acceptable Use Policy.
VIRUSES, HACKING AND OTHER OFFENCES
You must not misuse our site by knowingly introducing viruses, trojans, worms, logic bombs or other material which is malicious or technologically harmful. You must not attempt to gain unauthorised access to our site, the server on which our site is stored or any server, computer or database connected to our site. You must not attack our site via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of service attack.
By breaching this provision, you would commit a criminal offence under the Computer Misuse Act 1990. We will report any such breach to the relevant law enforcement authorities and we will co-operate with those authorities by disclosing your identity to them. In the event of such a breach, your right to use our site will cease immediately.
We will not be liable for any loss or damage caused by a distributed denial-of-service attack, viruses or other technologically harmful material that may infect your computer equipment, computer programs, data or other proprietary material due to your use of our site or to your downloading of any material posted on it, or on any website linked to it.
LINKING TO OUR SITE
You may link to our home page, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it, but you must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval or endorsement on our part where none exists.
You must not establish a link from any website that is not owned by you.
Our site must not be framed on any other site, nor may you create a link to any part of our site other than the home page. We reserve the right to withdraw linking permission without notice. The website from which you are linking must comply in all respects with the content standards set out in our Acceptable Use Policy.
If you wish to make any use of material on our site other than that set out above, please address your request to general@lutyenstrust.org.uk.
LINKS FROM OUR SITE
Where our site contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your information only. We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them.
JURISDICTION AND APPLICABLE LAW
The English courts will have exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising from, or related to, a visit to our site although we retain the right to bring proceedings against you for breach of these conditions in your country of residence or any other relevant country.
These terms of use and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with them or their subject matter or formation (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the law of England and Wales.
VARIATIONS
We may revise these terms of use at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we made, as they are binding on you. Some of the provisions contained in these terms of use may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on our site.
YOUR CONCERNS
If you have any concerns about material which appears on our site, please contact us at general@lutyenstrust.org.uk
ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY
Last Updated: 20 December 2013
This Acceptable Use Policy sets out the terms between you and us under which you may access our website www.lutyenstrust.org.uk (our site). This Acceptable Use Policy applies to all users of, and visitors to, our site.
Your use of our site means that you accept, and agree to abide by, all the policies in this Acceptable Use Policy, which supplement our Terms of Website Use.
Lutyenstrust.org.uk is a site operated by The Lutyens Trust (we or us).  We are a registered charity under charity number 3267765 and have our registered office at Goddards, Abinger Common, Dorking, Surrey, RH5 6JH.
1.PROHIBITED USES
You may use our site only for lawful purposes.  You may not use our site:
•In any way that breaches any applicable local, national or international law or regulation.
•In any way that is unlawful or fraudulent, or has any unlawful or fraudulent purpose or effect.
•For the purpose of harming or attempting to harm minors in any way.
•To send, knowingly receive, upload, download, use or re-use any material which does not comply with our content standards set out at 2 below.
•To transmit, or procure the sending of, any unsolicited or unauthorised advertising or promotional material or any other form of similar solicitation (spam).
•To knowingly transmit any data, send or upload any material that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time-bombs, keystroke loggers, spyware, adware or any other harmful programs or similar computer code designed to adversely affect the operation of any computer software or hardware.
You also agree:
•Not to reproduce, duplicate, copy or re-sell any part of our site in contravention of the provisions of our Terms of Website Use.
•Not to access without authority, interfere with, damage or disrupt any part of our site, any equipment or network on which our site is stored, any software used in the provision of our site, or any equipment or network or software owned or used by any third party.
2.CONTENT STANDARDS
These content standards apply to any and all material which you contribute to our site (contributions), and to any interactive services associated with it.
You must comply with the spirit of the following standards as well as the letter. The standards apply to each part of any contribution as well as to its whole.
Contributions must comply with applicable law in the UK and in any country from which they are posted.
Contributions must not:
•Infringe any copyright, database right or trade mark of any other person.
•Contain any material which is defamatory of any person.
•Contain any material which is obscene, offensive, hateful or inflammatory, or is likely to harass, upset, embarrass, alarm or annoy any other person.
•Be made in breach of any legal duty owed to a third party, such as a contractual duty or a duty of confidence.
•Promote any illegal activity.
•Advocate, promote or assist any unlawful act such as (by way of example only) copyright infringement or computer misuse.
3.SUSPENSION AND TERMINATION
We will determine, in our discretion, whether there has been a breach of this Acceptable Use Policy through your use of our site.  When a breach of this policy has occurred, we may take such action as we deem appropriate.
Failure to comply with this Acceptable Use Policy constitutes a material breach of the Terms of Website Use upon which you are permitted to use our site, and may result in our taking all or any of the following actions:
•Immediate, temporary or permanent withdrawal of your right to use our site;
•Immediate, temporary or permanent removal of any material uploaded by you to our site;
•Issue of a warning to you;
•Legal proceedings against you for reimbursement of all costs on an indemnity basis (including, but not limited to, reasonable administrative and legal costs) resulting from the breach;
•Further legal action against you; and/or
•Disclosure of such information to law enforcement authorities as we reasonably feel is necessary.
We exclude liability for actions taken in response to breaches of this Acceptable Use policy.  The responses described in this policy are not limited, and we may take any other action we reasonably deem appropriate.
4.CHANGES TO THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY
We may revise this Acceptable Use Policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we make, as they are legally binding on you. Some of the provisions contained in this Acceptable Use Policy may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on our site.
PRIVACY STATEMENT
Last Updated: 20 December 2013
This Privacy Statement forms part of the legally binding Terms of Website Use between you and The Lutyens Trust (us) and governs how we use your Personal Information on our site. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our users, and we strive to provide a safe and secure user experience. This Privacy Statement describes and explains how we collect and use online data.
By agreeing to the Terms of Website Use (and the Privacy Statement where applicable), you are consenting to the collection, storing, transmission, disclosure and use of your Personal Information as set out in this Privacy Statement.  To revoke your consent, please click here. If you do revoke your consent, your account and your information will be deleted.
The term “Personal Information” means any information that relates to you and that could be used, either directly or indirectly, to identify you.  Capitalised terms not otherwise defined below shall have the meaning given to them in the Terms of Website UseTerms of Website Use.
Please note that if you arrive on our site using an account from a supported social media platform, such as Facebook or Twitter, additional privacy policies and statements may apply to you as a user of that site.
We have set out below answers to the following questions regarding this Privacy Statement.
1.What Personal Information is collected through the site?
2.Who controls my Personal Information?
3.What are cookies, and how are they used to collect Personal Information?
4.How will my Personal Information be used?
5.What about other websites?
6.Is the Personal Information collected about me secure?
7.What happens when you change this Privacy Statement for the site?
8.Who can I contact about accessing, deleting or amending my Personal Information?
1.What Personal Information is collected through the Website?
We may collect and may use certain Personal Information about you in order to operate and provide access to our site.
By using the site, you agree that the site may collect other Personal Information about you, including but not limited to the following:
a.account and other information provided by a supported social media platform when you enter the site as a logged-in user of that platform;
b.any Personal Information that you may choose to provide when participating or publishing content on the site. Please do not include in your content any financial or sensitive Personal Information about you or any other person (including without limitation, social security numbers or other government issued identification numbers, information about an individual’s religious, philosophical or similar beliefs, racial or ethnic origin, health or sexual life, genetic code, addictions, political affiliation or political party membership, trade union membership or information about criminal offences or any other categories of Personal Information defined as sensitive under applicable data protection laws);
c.information about your usage of the site  (e.g., the pages you request and visit, the posts or content you publish, and your interaction with the site);
d.information obtained about you in the course of maintaining or supporting the site; and
e.information about your internet use, such as your IP address, the URLs of sites from which you arrive or leave the site, your type of browser, your operating system and your internet service provider (ISP). We may also collect information about your mobile provider and your mobile device.
2.Who controls my Personal Information?
Your Personal Information will be controlled by The Lutyens Trust. Our registered address is Goddards, Abinger Common, Dorking, Surrey, RH5 6JH. We can be contacted in relation to privacy queries at general@lutyenstrust.org.uk
3.What are cookies and how are they used to collect Information?
A cookie is a small text file stored on your hard drive containing information about you. We use cookies to enable functionality to be personalised by logging in. A cookie set by the site stores information linked to unique user identification number that enables the site to remember you when you return to visit the site or when you are logged in, in order to provide a consistent, secure and appropriate service. The cookies do not carry sensitive information identifying you individually and are used to remember menu layouts, to provide a consistent and secure form handling process for contact forms, and to measure trends in usage for the purposes of capacity planning and marketing. Some cookies will remain on the computer after you leave the site, whilst others will only last as long as your browser remains open.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying the settings in your browser. However, you may not be able to use all the features of the Website if cookies are disabled.
We may use other companies to set cookies on our websites, gather cookie information for us and serve advertisements on our websites.  In some cases, we will also use another company to operate web servers for our sites.  You can opt out of third party cookies by setting your browser to decline cookies.
Please note if you delete your browser cookies, your opt-out cookie, as well as any updates you may have made, will also be deleted. Additionally, if you change computers or web browsers, you will need to opt out again.
4.How will my Personal Information be used?
Any Personal Information that you submit, whether about yourself or others (with their consent) in the public area will be available to the entire site community globally.
In addition to other uses described below, we will have access to and may use Personal Information that you submit on, or otherwise provide in connection with, the site for administering and managing and providing other services in relation to the site, including but not limited to:
•facilitating your participation in the site,
•enabling you to share your content and communicate with other users,
•enabling us to communicate with you,
•customising the service we provide to you and other users,
•providing you any services that may be available on this site from time to time,
•monitoring compliance with the Terms of Website Use and complying with applicable law or regulations and our policies, and
•investigating any complaints about the use of the site.
We may also disclose Personal Information in order to protect our legal rights, privacy, safety, security or legitimate interests, or those of our affiliates, or our respective investors, directors, officers, employees, agents and suppliers.  These instances may include, but are not limited to: protecting the safety and security of  visitors to our websites or other properties; complying with our policies; enforcing the Terms of Website Use; complying with the law or regulations, or responding to a subpoena or other legal demand; responding to inquiries or requests from public authorities; permitting us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that it may sustain; protecting against fraud, crime, illegal activity, anti-money laundering, anti-terrorism, or for risk management purposes;  or otherwise in connection with legal, compliance, regulatory and investigative purposes.
If we appoint third parties to host, maintain, manage, or to provide other services in relation to the Website, then the Personal Information included in the Website may be accessed and used by these third parties to the extent necessary to fulfill their hosting, maintenance, managerial, and/or other functions. Where these third parties are located outside the EEA, we will ensure that they provide an adequate level of protection for your Personal Information.
We do not rent, sell or otherwise provide your Personal Information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your prior consent.
You understand and agree that the site and any Personal Information included on the Website may be hosted, maintained and accessed globally (including outside the EEA and in the US and including in countries that may not have data protection laws).
5.What about other websites?
As set out earlier in this Privacy Statement, if you arrive on our site using an account from a different social media platform, such as Facebook or Twitter, additional privacy policies and statements may apply to you as a user of that site. If you use the site using another social media platform account, we will be provided with Personal Information by that site. Our site may also contain links to other websites.
We are not responsible for the privacy or information security practices of other websites. You should carefully review the applicable privacy and information security policies and statements for any other websites to which you click through to via the Website.  This Privacy Statement applies solely to your Personal Information collected by this site.
6.Is the Personal Information collected about me secure?
The site uses reasonable physical, electronic, and procedural measures to safeguard information against loss, theft, and unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification.  Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee its security.
You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your password and other site registration information, and for controlling access to your email communications at all times.
7.What happens when you change this Privacy Statement for the site?
From time to time, we may revise this Privacy Statement.  Changes may be made for any number of reasons, including to reflect industry initiatives, changes in the law, and changes to the scope of the site, among other reasons.  You can tell when we last updated the Privacy Statement by checking the “Last Updated” legend at the beginning of the Privacy Statement. Your continued use of the Website will indicate your agreement to the new Privacy Statement.
8.Who can I contact about accessing, amending or deleting my Personal Information?
You may have certain rights with respect to the Personal Information which we hold about you including the right to access, correct (and sometimes, object to or delete) the information. If you would like to request deletion of your information or have questions or requests, please contact general@lutyenstrust.org.uk who will be able to guide you as to how to do this.
If you have any other questions concerning this Privacy Statement, you may submit them to general@lutyenstrust.org.uk or write to them at The Secretary to the Trustees, The Lutyens Trust, Goddards, Abinger Common, Dorking, Surrey RH5 6JH
ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY
Last Updated: 20 December 2013
This Acceptable Use Policy sets out the terms between you and us under which you may access our website www.lutyenstrust.org.uk (our site). This Acceptable Use Policy applies to all users of, and visitors to, our site.
Your use of our site means that you accept, and agree to abide by, all the policies in this Acceptable Use Policy, which supplement our Terms of Website UseTerms of Website Use.
Lutyenstrust.org.uk is a site operated by The Lutyens Trust (we or us).  We are a registered charity under charity number 3267765 and have our registered office at Goddards, Abinger Common, Dorking, Surrey, RH5 6JH.
1.PROHIBITED USES
You may use our site only for lawful purposes.  You may not use our site:
•In any way that breaches any applicable local, national or international law or regulation.
•In any way that is unlawful or fraudulent, or has any unlawful or fraudulent purpose or effect.
•For the purpose of harming or attempting to harm minors in any way.
•To send, knowingly receive, upload, download, use or re-use any material which does not comply with our content standards set out at 2 below.
•To transmit, or procure the sending of, any unsolicited or unauthorised advertising or promotional material or any other form of similar solicitation (spam).
•To knowingly transmit any data, send or upload any material that contains viruses, Trojan horses, worms, time-bombs, keystroke loggers, spyware, adware or any other harmful programs or similar computer code designed to adversely affect the operation of any computer software or hardware.
You also agree:
•Not to reproduce, duplicate, copy or re-sell any part of our site in contravention of the provisions of our Terms of Website UseTerms of Website Use.
•Not to access without authority, interfere with, damage or disrupt any part of our site, any equipment or network on which our site is stored, any software used in the provision of our site, or any equipment or network or software owned or used by any third party.
2.CONTENT STANDARDS
These content standards apply to any and all material which you contribute to our site (contributions), and to any interactive services associated with it.
You must comply with the spirit of the following standards as well as the letter. The standards apply to each part of any contribution as well as to its whole.
Contributions must comply with applicable law in the UK and in any country from which they are posted.
Contributions must not:
•Infringe any copyright, database right or trade mark of any other person.
•Contain any material which is defamatory of any person.
•Contain any material which is obscene, offensive, hateful or inflammatory, or is likely to harass, upset, embarrass, alarm or annoy any other person.
•Be made in breach of any legal duty owed to a third party, such as a contractual duty or a duty of confidence.
•Promote any illegal activity.
•Advocate, promote or assist any unlawful act such as (by way of example only) copyright infringement or computer misuse.
3.SUSPENSION AND TERMINATION
We will determine, in our discretion, whether there has been a breach of this Acceptable Use Policy through your use of our site.  When a breach of this policy has occurred, we may take such action as we deem appropriate.
Failure to comply with this Acceptable Use Policy constitutes a material breach of the Terms of Website UseTerms of Website Use upon which you are permitted to use our site, and may result in our taking all or any of the following actions:
•Immediate, temporary or permanent withdrawal of your right to use our site;
•Immediate, temporary or permanent removal of any material uploaded by you to our site;
•Issue of a warning to you;
•Legal proceedings against you for reimbursement of all costs on an indemnity basis (including, but not limited to, reasonable administrative and legal costs) resulting from the breach;
•Further legal action against you; and/or
•Disclosure of such information to law enforcement authorities as we reasonably feel is necessary.
We exclude liability for actions taken in response to breaches of this Acceptable Use policy.  The responses described in this policy are not limited, and we may take any other action we reasonably deem appropriate.
4.CHANGES TO THE ACCEPTABLE USE POLICY
We may revise this Acceptable Use Policy at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we make, as they are legally binding on you. Some of the provisions contained in this Acceptable Use Policy may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on our site.
Please make a donation to the Lutyens Trust
Scroll to top
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
